(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-04T12:56:29.417027",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Telolet, telolet, telolet, telolet!
Halo, everyone!
Hello, everyone!
Selamat datang di birthday show Ayunda Risu!
Welcome to Ayunda Risu's birthday show!
Gimana? Keren enggak, guys?
How is it? Isn't it cool, guys?
Cia, cia, yea!
Cha, cha, yeah!
Malam ini, guys, kalian diundang
Tonight, guys, you're invited
untuk ikut dalam penyanyian
to take part in a sing-along
sambil naik Risu Isekai Express.
while riding the Risu Isekai Express.
Kenapa sebutnya penyanyian?
Why call it a sing-along?
Karena kalian akan diajak pergi
Because you'll be taken
ke berbagai macam tempat bersama Risu sambil bernyanyi.
to various places with Risu while singing.
Jadi, kita akan berjalan-jalan mendaki gunung,
So, we'll go walking, climbing mountains,
melewati pantai, sambil bernyanyi bersama.
passing beaches, and singing together.
Terus, dapat dilihat juga nih, di pojok layar kalian
Also, as you can see in the corner of your screen
ada hashtag #RisuIsekaiExpress3D
there's the hashtag #RisuIsekaiExpress3D
yang bisa kalian pakai untuk membagikan pengalaman perjalanan...
that you can use to share your travel experiences...
...kalian bersama Risu Isekai Express.
...with the Risu Isekai Express.
perjalanan dengan hashtag di atas
Journey with the hashtag above
dan post di sosial media kalian ya!
and post it on your social media, okay!
Lihat nih, nih, nih, nih, nih!
Look at this, this, this, this, this!
Di sini Risu sudah siap untuk mengajak kalian berkeliling dengan truk kesayangan Risu!
Here Risu is ready to take you on a tour around with Risu's beloved truck!
Siapa yang sudah nggak sabar untuk pergi naik Risu Sekai Express?
Who can't wait to go ride the Risu Sekai Express?
Ayo teman-teman, kita let's go!
Come on friends, let's go!
Tarollet, tarollet, tarollet, tarollet!
Langsung aja ke lagu pertama enggak sih?
Shall we go straight to the first song?
Eh, bentar guys, ngaret! Kok ada suara telepon? Risu angkat dulu bentar ya, guys.
Wait guys, we're late! Why is there a phone call? Risu will pick it up for a moment, guys.
hari itu kulihat langit sore,
berandai jika ku seorang peri
That day I saw the evening sky,
wishing if I were a fairy
'kan ku terbang langsung kunjungi mu,
lewati lembah gurun bersalju
I'd fly straight to visit you,
across valleys and snowy deserts
meskipun rapor ku selalu merah,
aku mau jadi fisikawan
Even though my report card is always red,
I want to be a physicist
'kan ku hilangkan jarak dan waktu,
agar aku selalu bersamamu
I will eliminate distance and time,
so that I can always be with you
walau hanya sebatas video call saja,
sebatas kirim foto kucing saja
Even if it's just a video call,
just sending cat photos
sebatas ucapan pagi, oh senangnya,
lama-lama memupuk jadi cinta
Just morning greetings, oh how joyful,
gradually cultivating into love
malam itu kau ajak ku berkencan
di atas perahu venessia
That night you asked me on a date
on a Venetian boat
tak sengaja tangan kita berdua bertemu,
rasaku menggebu di dada
Our hands accidentally met,
my heart raced in my chest
ingat ku akan mimpi malam tadi,
namun hari kini sudah pagi
I remember the dream last night,
but today has already dawned
mungkin tak lama lagi kita berjumpa,
arungi anganku bersamamu
Maybe we will meet soon,
sail through my thoughts with you
walau hanya sebatas video call saja,
sebatas kirim foto kucing saja
Even if it's just a video call,
just sending cat photos
sebatas ucapan pagi, oh senangnya,
lama-lama memupuk jadi cinta
Just morning greetings, oh how joyful,
gradually cultivating into love
walau hanya sebatas video call saja,
sebatas kirim foto kucing saja
Even if it's just a video call,
just sending cat photos
sebatas ucapan pagi, oh senangnya,
lama-lama memupuk jadi cinta
Just morning greetings, oh how joyful,
gradually cultivating into love
walau hanya sebatas video call saja,
sebatas kirim foto kucing saja
Even if it's just a video call,
just sending cat photos
sebatas ucapan pagi, oh senangnya,
lama-lama memupuk jadi cinta
Just morning greetings, oh how joyful,
gradually cultivating into love
wasureru rarenu mono dake ga utsukushiku wanai desho
Not only unforgettable things are beautiful
wasureru koto bakari ga utsukushiku wanai deshou
Not only forgetting things is beautiful
kanashii koto bakari ga jinsei dewa nai no deshou
Surely not only sad things make up life
fusari to te yoru kobito wa kurabe yuku deshou
Tying hands and night's people will compare
aranami no naka de nagasare zu irareta deshou
Could we stay without being washed away in rough waves?
minasoko ni dezazu anatato gattashou joushidai
At the bottom of the water, showing our youth with you
sayonara suru koro shira reru to wa
When we say goodbye, what is known is...
bachi kyuu hiza no kazu wo kazoete itai no kazu wo aru
Counting the number of beatings and knees...
hitotsu wa mariko yubi wa itoshi sa nazone
One is the ring finger, beloved names
shurei koto mo arimashou arata na sei mo arimashou
There might be praise, there might be a new life
それでも赤い糸 追っかけているのだろうね
Even so, you're chasing the red thread of fate, aren't you?
そこ知れぬものだけに怯えるのではないでしょ
You aren't just frightened by the unknown, are you?
届かぬものばかりが妬ましくはないでしょ
It's not just things out of reach that you envy, right?
優しいことばかりが優しさではないのでしょう
Kindness isn't just about gentle words alone, is it?
二人とて赤裸々ではこそばゆいでしょう
Being completely bare with one another is a bit ticklish, right?
跳ねよ跳ねよ 人並みを望み
Leap, leap, desiring to be like everyone else,
人並みに拒まれては
yet rejected when you try to fit in—
皆そこを目指す まだがむしゃらだった少女時代
Girlhood days when everyone aimed for that, still reckless.
向こうでいたころはどう? 尖っていたの?
How was it back then when you were over there? Were you edgy?
髪の長さそろえて爪の先を塗り直す
Aligning the length of my hair, repainting my fingertips.
あどけない唇は色めき立ったのね
My innocent lips became flushed with color, didn't they?
叶うこともありましょう 変わる人もおりましょう
Dreams can come true, and people can change.
それ故慰め舟で 浮いられないのでしょう
That's probably why we can't just float away on a boat of consolation.
跳ねよ跳ねよ 水面に映って
Leap, leap, reflected on the water's surface,
傷の数を数えて 痛みの数よる
Counting the number of wounds, the number of pains at night—
一つ余り子指は 愛しさが募るね
One extra pinky finger makes the affection grow stronger.
悔うこともありましょう 私のせいもありましょう
There may be regrets, and it might be my fault too.
いつかは赤い糸 絶ち切るのだろうね
Someday, the red thread of fate will be severed, won't it?
花びらに囁きの 哀れみから口付けを
A whisper on the petals, a kiss born of pity—
懐かしんで初めて 知りゆくのだろうね
Perhaps for the first time with nostalgia, we come to know it.
まだ動くこともあるましょう 誰かのせいじゃないでしょう
There may still be times when things move; it's probably nobody's fault.
難しいものですね 愛するということは
Loving someone is such a difficult thing, isn't it?
君の虜になってしまえばきっと
If I were to become your prisoner, surely
この夏は充実するのもっと
this summer would be even more fulfilling.
もう戻れなくたって忘れないで
Even if I can never go back, don't forget that.
何年経っても言えない
Even after all these years, I can't say it.
後悔したってかまわない
Even if I regret it, I don't care.
でも言葉はここまで出てるの
But the words have come this far.
ねえ summertime
Hey, summertime.
海岸通りを歩きたい
I want to walk along the seaside avenue.
ドライブだってしてみたい
I want to try going for a drive, too.
ただ視線を合わせてほしいの ねえ summertime
I just want you to meet my gaze, hey summertime.
夜明けまで海辺走って 潮騒に包まれたいね
Running along the beach until dawn, embraced by the sound of the waves.
彼女の仕草が甘いね
Her gestures are so sweet, aren't they?
君の虜になってしまえばきっと
If I were to become your prisoner, surely
この夏は充実するのもっと
this summer would be even more fulfilling.
噂の dreaming girl 忘れないで
Don't forget the rumored dreaming girl.
でも気持ちを伝えてしまえばいつか
But if I ever convey these feelings, someday
この夢は覚めてしまうのだろうな
this dream will surely awaken and end.
青い影が揺れる街角と
With the street corner where blue shadows sway...
占いなんて信じない
I don't believe in fortune-telling.
運命なんてあるわけない
There's no such thing as destiny.
ただ本当のことを知りたいの ねえ summertime
I just want to know the truth, hey summertime.
近づく距離にも気づかない
Not even noticing the distance closing between us,
胸の高鳴りごまかせない
I can't hide the pounding of my heart.
でも昔と変わらずにぶいのね ねえ summertime
But you're as dense as ever, hey summertime.
思い出は色褪せたって
Even if memories have faded,
惚れた腫れたの中がいいね
falling in love and bickering is nice, isn't it?
彼女の笑顔が憎いね
Her smiling face is so frustratingly cute, isn't it?
君の虜になってしまえばきっと この夏は充実するのもっと
If I could just become your captive, this summer would be even more fulfilling
もう戻れなくてだって忘れないで
Can't go back anymore, so please don't forget
何年経っても言えない 後悔したって構わない
Even after years pass I can't say it, I don't care if I'll regret it
でも言葉はここまで出てるの ねぇ サマータイム
But the words are right here on my tongue, hey, Summertime
岸壁通りを歩きたい ドライブだってしてみたい
I want to walk down the coast road, I want to go on a drive with you
君の虜になってしまえばきっと この夏は充実するのもっと
If I could just become your captive, this summer would be even more fulfilling
もう戻れなくてだって忘れないで
Can't go back anymore, so please don't forget
岸壁通りを歩きたい ドライブだってしてみたい
I want to walk down the coast road, I want to go on a drive with you
でも言葉はここまで出てるの ねぇ サマータイム
But the words are right here on my tongue, hey, Summertime
夜明けまで海辺走って 潮騒に包まれたいね
I want to run through the shore all night and listen to the tides
彼女の仕草が甘いね 君の虜になってしまえばきっと
Every move she makes is sweet, if I could just become your captive
この夏は充実するのもっと
this summer would be even more fulfilling
岸壁通りを歩きたい ドライブだってしてみたい
I want to walk down the coast road, I want to go on a drive with you
ただ視線を合わせてほしいの ねぇ サマータイム
And I just want you to look at my eyes, hey, Summertime
Wao! Terole-terole-terole-terole!
Whoa! Terole-terole-terole-terole!
Gimana lagunya barusan, guys? Seru gak? Serulah!
How was the song just now, guys? Was it fun? Of course it was!
Jadi, tadi Risu sudah menyanyikan lagu dengan judul Bathtub dan juga Summertime.
So, just now Risu sang songs titled Bathtub and also Summertime.
Kalian pasti udah pernah dengar lagu Summertime, kan?
You guys must have heard the song Summertime before, right?
Ya, pasti udah pernah lah ya.
Yeah, you definitely have, right?
Dua lagu barusan tuh, kalau kata Risu sih, cocok banget dengan tempat yang kita kunjungi sekarang, guys.
Those two songs just now, if you ask Risu, fit really well with the place we're visiting right now, guys.
Kan, kalau di pantai kayak gini nih, lagunya kan juga harus yang bersemangat, terus juga fresh, gitu gak sih?
Right, if it's at a beach like this, the songs should also be energetic and fresh, right?
Terus, guys, gimana tadi penampilan truknya Risu?
Also, guys, how was Risu's truck performance just now?
Selain bisa dipakai buat bepergian, truknya juga bisa berubah jadi panggung gitu, guys. Wah, keren banget gak sih?
Aside from being used for traveling, the truck can also turn into a stage, guys. Wow, isn't that super cool?
Eh, spoiler dikit ya, truknya nanti gak cuma bisa satu model loh, guys! Jadi jangan pergi dulu dan tonton acaranya sampai habis, ya!
Um, a little spoiler, okay? The truck later won't just have one model, guys! So don't go away yet and watch the show until the end, okay?
Eits, jangan lupa buat screenshot yang banyak dan post di sosial media dengan hashtag di atas! Kalau gak, nanti truknya gak lanjut jalan loh!
Wait, don't forget to take lots of screenshots and post them on social media with the hashtag above! If not, the truck won't keep driving, you know!
Weh, udah pada banyak aja nih yang nge-post. Ya udah, kalau gitu kita let's go ke tempat selanjutnya!
Whoa, there are already so many people posting. Alright, if so, let's go to the next place!
Telole-telole-telole-telole!
Terole-terole-terole-terole!
I feel like I'm losing hope
In my body and my soul
And the sky, it looks so ominous
And as time comes to a halt
Silence starts to overflow
My cries are inconspicuous
Tell me, God, are you punishing me?
Is this the price I'm paying for my past mistakes?
This is my redemption song
I need you more than ever right now
Can you hear me now?
'Cause we're gonna shout it loud,
even if our words seem meaningless.
It's like I'm carrying the weight of the world.
I wish that someway, somehow...
that I could save every one of us,
but the truth is that I'm only one girl.
Maybe if I keep believing,
my dreams will come to life,
come to life.
After all the laughter fades,
signs of life all washed away,
I can still, still feel a gentle breeze.
No matter how hard I pray,
signs of warning still remain,
and life has become my enemy.
Tell me God, are you punishing me?
Is this the price I'm paying for my past mistakes?
This is my redemption song.
I need you more than ever right now.
Can you hear me now?
'Cause we're gonna shout it loud,
even if our words seem meaningless.
It's like I'm carrying the weight of the world.
I wish that someway, somehow...
that I could save every one of us,
but the truth is that I'm only one girl.
Maybe if I keep believing,
my dreams will come to life,
come to life.
'Cause we're gonna shout it loud,
even if our words seem meaningless.
It's like I'm carrying the weight of the world.
I wish that someway, somehow...
that I could save every one of us,
but the truth is that I'm only one girl.
Still, we're gonna shout it loud,
even if our words seem meaningless.
It's like I'm carrying the weight of the world.
I hope that someway, somehow...
that I could save every one of us,
but the truth is that I'm only one girl.
Maybe if I keep believing,
my dreams will come to life,
come to life.
shul parel moi him...
shul parel moi him
From the village of Shur...
ar , jaruk no is in
the girl who lost her home,
dah galach dal fouir
The girl who was raised by wolves, the girl who fights
malech foir dir azlad erenj boir
Her companion is a magical song
hiu o tantiera had rei kun harech fala le ya boi
Her companion is a dream of the distant land
hiu o migenda yaka chren no hei kaine rekara
Her companion is a magical song
hiu o tantiera had rei kun harech fala le ya boi
Her companion is a dream of the faraway mountain
hiu o migenda ya kochren no hei yalma
Kaine, the girl who lost everything
tei koi miren tara baira tru
From the village of Shur...
shul parel moi him
ar , jaruk no is in
the girl who lost her home,
dah galach dal fouir
The girl who was raised by wolves, the girl who fights
malech foir dir azlad erenj boir
Her companion is a magical song
hiu o tantiera had rei kun harech fala le ya boi
Her companion is a dream of the distant land
hiu o migenda yaka chren no hei kaine rekara
Her companion is a magical song
hiu o tantiera had rei kun harech fala le ya boi
Her companion is a dream of the faraway mountain
hiu o migenda ya kochren no hei yalma
Kaine, the girl who lost everything
tei koi miren tara baira tru
From the village of Shur...
もうあなたから愛されることも
I will no longer be loved or needed by you
必要とされることもない
And now I will be alone, like this
そして私はこうして一人ぼっちで
What did you say at that time?
あの時あなたはなんて言ったの?
Words that can't reach me hover in the air
届かない言葉は宙を舞う
I know, I repeat that again, expecting something that will never be fulfilled
わかってるのに今日もしてしまう
Do not go, hold my hand tightly
叶わぬ願いごとを
Say, "I will still go, with you"
離さないで ぎゅっと手を握っていて
The hand holding my hand was so warm and soft
あなたと二人 続くと言って
You always make me angry and emotional and until finally I cry
繋いだその手は温かくて 優しかった
But I like to see your face when you say sorry
あなたはいつもそうやって私を
Do not go, hug me tightly
怒らせて最後に泣かすんだけど
Hug with all your feelings, I want to be in your arms
だけど後になって ごめんねっていうその顔
With our foreheads leaning against each other, we begin to close our eyes
好きだった
Do you know that we will never see each other again?
離さないで ぎゅっと そう思いっきり
Do not go, hold my hand tight, I love you
あなたの腕の中にいたい
Can you smile for me one more time before your warmth begins to disappear?
ふたりで おでこをあわせながら
Hug me tightly
もうあなたから愛されることも
No longer being loved by you,
必要なこともない
Or ever being needed,
そして私はこうして一人ぼっちで
And here I am, all alone like this.
あの時あなたは何て言ったの？
What was it you said to me back then?
届かない言葉は宙を舞う
The words that won't reach dance in the air.
わかってるのに
Even though I know,
今日もしてしまう
today too I end up
叶わぬ願いごとを
wishing for things that won't come true.
離さないで
Don't let me go,
ぎゅっと 手を握っていて
hold my hand tightly,
あなたと二人 続くと言って
and tell me we'll go on together.
繋いだその手は温かくて 優しかった
The hand we joined was warm and gentle.
あなたはいつもそうやって私を
You were always like that,
怒らせて最後に泣かすんだ
making me angry and ending up making me cry.
だけど後になって
But afterwards,
ごめんねって言うその顔
that face saying 'sorry'...
好きだった
...I really loved.
Telolet, telolet, telolet, telolet!
Siapa yang suka driving sambil lihat pemandangan, dancing along sama lagu yang lagi diputar di music player?
Who likes driving while looking at the scenery, dancing along to the song playing on the music player?
Aku, aku, aku, aku!
Me, me, me, me!
Barusan juga kalian kan udah dengar lagu-lagu yang menyentuh hati sambil ditemani pemandangan alami gitu. Iya enggak?
Just now, you guys already heard heart-touching songs accompanied by natural scenery like that, right?
Lagu-lagu sebelumnya tuh lagu favorit Risu semua, guys.
The previous songs were all Risu's favorite songs, guys.
Pasti kalian udah pada tahu judulnya kan ya?
You guys must already know the titles, right?
Weh, pasti kalian terharu banget sih dengerinnya tadi.
Man, you must've been so touched listening to it earlier.
Terus, setelah melewati pemandangan yang asri, kita masuk ke daerah perkotaan nih, guys.
Then, after passing through the lush scenery, we enter the urban area, guys.
Enak banget sih kayaknya nyetir di perkotaan sambil nyanyi-nyanyi gitu, apalagi kalau lagunya yang syahdu gitu, guys.
It feels so nice driving in the city while singing along, especially if the song is soulful like this, guys.
Ayo lanjut nyanyi bareng Risu sambil lihat pemandangan kota.
Come on, keep singing along with Risu while looking at the city scenery.
Ayo guys, let's go!
Come on guys, let's go!
Telolet, telolet, telolet, telolet!
あの日持って帰ったライターでタバコに火をつける
I lit a cigarette with a lighter I brought home that day,
煙で前が見えなくなった
And the smoke made the front invisible.
換気扇の音消えた
The sound of the ventilation fan faded away,
部屋に残った缶ビール
Canned beer left in the room,
乾かし続けた下着がうなだれた私に見えた
And my damp underwear hanging out looked like a drooping me.
ぐちゃぐちゃになった部屋
A messy room,
死体みたいなぬいぐるみ
Stuffed animals like corpses,
今夜はパレード
Tonight is a parade.
弱めの冷房に揺れた前髪が あの夏を何度も思い出させる
My bangs swaying in the weak air conditioning remind me of that summer over and over.
ねむるまちに行こう
Let's go to the sleeping town,
ねむるまちに行こうよ
Let's go to the sleeping town.
今夜も街灯は耐えきれずに目を閉じるんだ
Tonight, too, streetlights close their eyes, unable to endure.
砕けて散った葛藤思想
Shattered and scattered conflicting thoughts,
ドラマで見たんだ
I saw them in a drama.
正義は必ず勝って
That justice always wins—
正義って何なの？
What is justice anyway?
わからないことはわからないよ
I don't know what I don't know.
まだ子どもだし大人じゃないし
I'm still a child, not an adult.
今日も天井を見ていた変わらない風景だ
Today too I looked at the ceiling; the scenery hasn't changed.
くだけで散った
A crumbling town,
ドラマで見たんだ
I saw in a drama.
最近を必ず隠すって 正規って何なの？
Recently always hiding it, what is justice anyway?
わかんないことはわかんないよ まだ子どもだし 大人じゃないし
I don't know what I don't know, I'm still a child, not an adult.
今日も天井を見ていた 変わらない部屋だ
Today too I looked at the ceiling, an unchanged room.
ねむるまちに行こう
Let's go to the sleeping town,
ねむるまちに行こうよ 今夜は向かいの ビルは布団に潜るんだ
Let's go to the sleeping town, tonight the building opposite is diving into the futon.
ねむるまちに行こう ねむるまちに行こうよ
Let's go to the sleeping town, let's go to the sleeping town.
もうすぐ終電だ
It's almost the last train,
さよならって言えた気がしたんだ
I felt like I could say goodbye.
眠る街をゆこう
Let's go through the sleeping city,
もうすぐ終点だよ
We'll be at the final stop soon.
さようなら
Farewell.
ありふれた私という協奏曲をなぞらえる日々
Day after day, I trace the commonplace concerto that is me.
それとなく指揮棒に合わせれば保障される調和
If I casually follow the baton, harmony is guaranteed.
ダウンビート
Downbeat.
眠る街をゆこう
Let's go through the sleeping city,
もう良いよ、疲れたよ
I'm done, I'm exhausted.
じゃあ、またね
Well then, see you later.
またね
See you later.
割とストイックで古典的な優等生
A rather stoic, classical honors student,
でもアップビートはアドリブで行かなくちゃ退屈でしょう
But if you don't ad-lib the upbeat, it'd be boring, wouldn't it?
楽譜通りの日常に枯れていくこの命ならば
If this life is withering away in a routine according to the score,
いっそ背徳の渦に溺れてしまいたい
I'd rather drown in a whirlpool of immorality.
ピアノ×フォルテ×スキャンダル
[Title: Piano x Forte x Scandal]
ありふれた私という協奏曲をなぞらえる日々
Day after day, I trace the commonplace concerto that is me,
それとなく指揮棒に合わせれば保障される調和
If I casually follow the baton, harmony is guaranteed.
ダウンビート
Downbeat.
割とストイックで古典的な優等生
A rather stoic, classical honors student,
でもアップビートはアドリブで行かなくちゃ退屈でしょう
But if you don't ad-lib the upbeat, it'd be boring, wouldn't it?
楽譜通りの日常に枯れていくこの命ならば
If this life is withering away in a routine according to the score,
いっそ背徳の渦に溺れてしまいたい
I'd rather drown in a whirlpool of immorality.
その指に光る愛の証さえ消え入るそうな程優しく囁いた言葉は禁断の小夜曲
Even the proof of love shining on your finger—words whispered so gently they might fade away are a forbidden serenade.
加速する愛のリズム突き詰めて確かめ合うように
Pushing the accelerating rhythm of love to the limit, as if testing each other,
今夜はフォルティシモでもいい
We can reach fortissimo tonight.
強く強く抱き締めて
Hold me tight, tight,
重なり合うこの声は闇に溶けて消えていくから
Because our overlapping voices will melt into the darkness and vanish.
きっと大丈夫よ何も悪いことじゃない
So don't worry, we're not doing anything wrong.
毎日忙しく瞳を閉じれば
Every day, if I close my eyes in the busyness,
本当はあなたの言葉が恋しい
I actually long for your words.
そんなの良くないよなんてね
"That's no good," you might say, but
友達は言うけれど
Friends say that, but
ああそんな言葉じゃ私のカワキがうるおうことなどないわ
Ah, such words won't quench my thirst at all.
可愛いげないセリフで不埒に乱れ出す
Uncute lines recklessly running wild,
その指に光る愛の証さえ消え入りそうな程優しく
Even the proof of love shining on that finger, whispering so gently it might fade away—
囁いた言葉は禁断の小夜曲
The whispered words are a forbidden serenade.
加速する愛のリズム突き詰めて確かめ合うようにとに角は
Pushing the accelerating rhythm of love to the limit, to test each other, anyway—
ポルタメントでもいい強く強く抱き締めて
Portamento is fine, hold me tight, tight.
重なり合うこの声は闇に溶けて消えていくから
Because our overlapping voices will melt into the darkness and vanish.
加速する愛のリズム突き詰めて
Pushing the accelerating rhythm of love to the limit,
確かめ合うようにとに角はポルタメントでもいい
To test each other, anyway, portamento is fine.
強く強く抱き締めて重なり合うこの声は
Hold me tight, tight, our overlapping voices—
闇に溶けて消えていくからきっと大丈夫よ
Will melt into the darkness and vanish, so it's definitely okay.
何も悪いことじゃない
We're not doing anything wrong.
どうだった？言えなれば灰色だったんだ
"How was it? To put it simply, it was gray."
今日から変えなきゃなって言ってどれ程経つのかさ
"How long has it been since I said I need to change starting today?"
地を払った 退屈な原っぱ
"I swept the ground, a boring field."
抜け出せるなら 明日は都市の花
"If I can break out, tomorrow is the city's flower."
幼気な動機は よりによってと言われるがままに
"My naive motives, just as they say, of all things,"
ビードロの目に 映る宮古のネイビー
"Navy of Miyako reflected in glass eyes"
頭上脱兎の如くいられば 枯れるまで慄る
"Like a startled rabbit overhead, trembling until I wither away"
バッドマナーも気にならない 眠らない街で生きる
"Without caring about bad manners, living in a sleepless city"
亜空間に連ねる摩天楼 行ったり来たりなfancy
"Skyscrapers stretching into sub-space, a back-and-forth fancy"
頭振られ junkie
"Head-banging junkie"
あっという間に散りゆく破天荒
"Extravagance scattering in the blink of an eye"
踏んだり蹴ったりの万里 その先の甘美
"A long journey of trials and tribulations, the sweetness beyond"
巡り巡るメトロ いつかの夢見たこの迷路を
"Roaming the revolving metro, this maze I once dreamed of"
この夜 make it out これは運命と
"Make it out of this night, calling it fate"
遠く時を止めることのない通りを
"Along the street where time never stops"
walk walk walk around
眠れない夜 明かそうよ
"Let's spend this sleepless night awake"
ステップタラッタ 踊れる音なら
"Step taratta, if it's music we can dance to"
重なる鼓動 地下裏何処へででも
"Overlapping heartbeats, to wherever underground"
期待とか未来とかわからない ただ夢を見続けたい
"Not knowing about expectations or future, I just want to keep dreaming"
虹色graffiti 離れないよねネオンのグラビティ
"Rainbow graffiti, inseparable from neon gravity"
このフラットな夜変えるから 雑踏の渦乗せられたら
"Because I'll change this flat night, if caught in the vortex of the crowd"
脱兎の如くいられば 枯れるまで慄る
"Like a startled rabbit, trembling until I wither away"
巡り巡るメトロ いつかの夢見たこの迷路を
"Roaming the revolving metro, this maze I once dreamed of"
この夜 make it out これは運命と
"Make it out of this night, calling it fate"
遠く時を止めることのない通りを
"Along the street where time never stops"
walk walk walk around
眠れない夜 明かそうよ
"Let's spend this sleepless night awake"
ステップタラッタ 踊れる音なら
"Step taratta, if it's music we can dance to"
重なる鼓動 地下裏何処へででも
"Overlapping heartbeats, to wherever underground"
期待とか未来とかわからない ただ夢を見続けたい
"Not knowing about expectations or future, I just want to keep dreaming"
虹色graffiti 離れないよねネオンのグラビティ
"Rainbow graffiti, inseparable from neon gravity"
このフラットな夜変えるから
"Because I'll change this flat night,"
街で生きる 亜空間に連ねる摩天楼
"Living in the city, skyscrapers stretching into sub-space"
行ったり来たりなfancy 頭振られ junkie
"Back-and-forth fancy, head-banging junkie"
あっという間に散りゆく破天荒
"Extravagance scattering in the blink of an eye"
踏んだり蹴ったりの万里 その先の甘美
"A long journey of trials and tribulations, the sweetness beyond"
右も左もダビー いつ日の光がさす日
"Right and left both dubby, the day when sunlight shines"
ズドーンだとどんな時よ 揺られたら
"If it's a boom, whenever it is, if shaken,"
枯れるまで煽る
"fanning until it withers"
バットマナーも気にしない
"Without caring about bad manners"
眠らない街で生きる 亜空間に連ねる摩天楼
"Living in a sleepless city, skyscrapers stretching into sub-space"
行ったり来たりなfancy 頭振られ junkie
"Back-and-forth fancy, head-banging junkie"
踏んだり蹴ったりの万里 その先の甘美
"A long journey of trials and tribulations, the sweetness beyond"
右も左もダビー いつ日の光がさす日
"Right and left both dubby, the day when sunlight shines"
Waw! Lagu apa tuh, guys?
"Woah! What song is that, guys?"
Lagu siapa tu?
"Whose song is that?"
Apa? I am the Risu?
"What? I am the Risu?"
Waw, keren banget gak sih lagunya?
"Woah, isn't the song so cool?"
Oh my god! I am the Risu rilis lagu baru!
"Oh my god! I am the Risu is releasing a new song!"
Hehehe, eit, sabar!
"Hehehe, wait, patience!"
Risu mau bagi info lagunya, guys, ke kalian dulu nih di sosial media.
"Risu wants to share info about the song first, guys, with you all on social media."
Ehm, agak susah sih pos sambil nyupir, guys. Tapi tenang!
"Uhm, it's a bit hard posting while driving, guys. But relax!"
Risu kan supir truk profesional. Jadi aman!
"Risu is a professional truck driver. So it's safe!"
Hop!
Tada! Sudah deh!
"Tada! Done!"
Kalian bisa cek info tentang lagunya di sosial media sekarang ya, guys.
"You guys can check info about the song on social media now, guys."
Apa? Kalian belum bisa lihat?
"What? You guys can't see it yet?"
Hah? Enggak mau beranjak dari layar?
"Huh? Don't want to move away from the screen?"
Nih, nih, nih, Risu kasih lihat ya, nih, guys.
"Here, here, here, Risu will show you, look, guys."
Ini dia, guys, lagu baru Risu yang berjudul 'Metropolis'!
"This is it, guys, Risu's new song titled 'Metropolis'!"
Dari judulnya aja udah keliatan sih kalau lagunya tuh cocok...
"Just from the title, you can already tell the song fits..."
banget sama vibe perkotaan gitu, guys.
so much with that urban vibe, guys.
Terus, kalian nyadar nggak sih?
Also, do you guys realize?
Judulnya kalau dibaca pakai logat Jepang, guys,
The title, if read with a Japanese accent, guys,
cara bacanya tuh jadi Metropolisu.
the way to read it becomes "Metropolisu".
Metropolisu, jadi di judulnya ada nama Risu-nya gitu, guys.
Metropolisu, so in the title there's Risu's name in it, guys.
Keren kan? Eh, kerenlah.
Cool, right? Eh, cool.
Terus lagunya sengaja dibuat up-beat biar bisa bikin kalian semangat gitu, guys, pas berangkat atau pulang sekolah, kerja, DLL gitulah.
And the song was deliberately made upbeat so it can make you guys feel energized when leaving or coming home from school, work, etc., like that.
Eh, habis itu lagunya juga cocok banget buat nemenin kalian jalan-jalan di malam hari gitu, guys. Hahaha!
Eh, after that the song is also really suitable to accompany you guys walking around at night, guys. Hahaha!
Nah, lagu sekeren ini tuh dibuat oleh produser musik yang namanya Shishi Shishisan.
Well, a song as cool as this was made by a music producer named Shishi Shishisan.
Bukan Shishishi ya, guys. Bukan Shishishi ketawa bapak-bapak, guys.
Not Shishishi, guys. Not Shishishi like an old man's laugh, guys.
Buat yang udah nggak sabar pengen dengerin lagunya lagi, guys, lagunya akan rilis di platform musik digital favorit kalian masing-masing di jam 00:00 waktu setempat.
For those of you who can't wait to listen to the song again, guys, the song will be released on your respective favorite digital music platforms at 00:00 local time.
Nanti waktu kalian sudah dengar lagunya di jam 00:00, langsung share yang banyak di grup WA keluarga, sekolah, kantor, terus apa ya? Grup sosmed, forum sosmed, pokoknya semuanya lah!
Later when you guys have heard the song at 00:00, immediately share it a lot in family, school, office WhatsApp groups, then what? Social media groups, social media forums, basically everything!
Biar makin banyak yang dengerin, guys. Terus buat yang sudah dengar, jangan lupa lupung terus lagunya ya, guys. Hahaha!
So that more people will listen, guys. Then for those who have heard, don't forget to keep looping the song, guys. Hahaha!
Eits, tunggu dulu. Perjalanan kita masih belum selesai ya, guys.
Eits, wait a minute. Our journey is still not over, guys.
Masih ada satu tempat lagi yang belum kita kunjungi.
There is still one more place we haven't visited.
Risu juga masih mau nyanyi-nyanyi bareng kalian nih, guys. Jadi kita lanjut yuk.
Risu also still wants to sing along with you guys, guys. So let's continue.
Telot telot telot telot!
Telolet, telolet, telolet, telolet!
目合わせ 始まる 品定め
Matching gazes, starting the appraisal,
不足したままの 意思疎通
Communication left insufficient,
無意味な 称賛 満足気
Meaningless praise, looking satisfied,
疲弊の見本市
A sample fair of exhaustion.
虚ろに飾る 紙面上
Decorated emptily on paper surfaces,
凹凸に振舞敷いた 詭弁
Sophistry swaying over unevenness.
拉げた顔を 嘲笑れて
With a pinched face being sneered at,
貼り付けられた顔が 剥離されていく
The pasted-on face is peeling away.
完膚無きまでに 壊れた個の盤 覆う手は？
Hands covering the broken individual board beyond recognition?
刻まれた皺 擦り減る靴底 咽び 答えを
Engraved wrinkles, worn-out soles, sobbing for the answer.
至上主義アドトラックで 四六時中を 駆け回る
Running around 24/7 in a supreme ad truck,
所詮使い捨ての 消耗品だと？
As a disposable commodity after all?
おっとり好い気になるなよ
Don't get too complacent leisurely,
パッと打ち上げてやれ 夜を呑み込む 星の花
Fire them up in a flash, star flowers swallowing the night,
また弥生に積み重ねられていく 祈り丸め投放る
Piled up again in Yayoi, prayers crumpled and tossed away.
最終尾の補欠競走
Supplementary race at the very end,
鋭利な追撃 板挟み
Sharp pursuit, caught between a rock and a hard place,
息詰まる下り天井
Breath-suffocating descending ceiling,
窮地の袋小路
Dead end in a desperate situation.
雨ニモ負ケズ 風ニモ負ケズ
Not losing to the rain, not losing to the wind,
錆び付いて腐食する 常識
Common sense rusting and corroding,
蝕みを増した 歯車は
The gears that increased their rot,
規格外の線へと 見切られていく
Are being written off toward out-of-spec lines.
変わり映え無い陳腐な烙印 晴らす手は？
Hands clearing the unchanging, trite stigma?
弾かれた枠 擦り抜ける篩 咽び 答えを
A sifter slipping through rejected boundaries, sobbing for the answer.
至上主義アドトラックで 唯一無二を 吊下る
Hanging the one and only in a supreme ad truck,
所詮役立たずの 代用品だと？
As a useless substitute after all?
おい今に見とけよ
Hey, just you wait and see now,
パッと仕掛けてやれ 夜に雪崩る 星の花
Set it off in a flash, star flowers avalanche into the night,
また一つ指で押開いていく 祈り横へ滑らす
Pushing open one more finger at a time, sliding prayers aside.
閉塞した亭の環状線 逃れる手は？
Hands escaping the loop line of the blocked pavilion?
均された理想 押し退く現実 咽び 答えを
Flattened ideal, pushing aside reality, sobbing for the answer.
至上主義アドトラックで 四六時中を 駆け回る
Running around 24/7 in a supreme ad truck,
所詮使い捨ての 消耗品だと？
As a disposable commodity after all?
おっとり好い気になるなよ
Don't get too complacent leisurely,
パッと打ち上げてやれ 夜を呑み込む 星の花
Fire them up in a flash, star flowers swallowing the night,
所詮役立たずの 代用品だと？
As a useless substitute after all?
おい今に見とけよ
Hey, just you wait and see now,
パッと仕掛けてやれ 夜に揺蕩う 星の花
Set it off in a flash, star flowers wavering in the night,
また空に散ばめられていく 祈り求め舞上がる
Scattered across the sky once more, prayers seeking and soaring up.
ラララ
La la la
チート、gifted、荒技、wanted
Cheat code, gifted, looking at a wanted
禁忌、禁じ手、明らかな盲点
Taboo when the gong hits
反則、異次元、この世の中のものでは無いです
Foul play, out of this world, not of this earth
無理ゲー、それ聞いてないって...
No way, you didn't say that...
ay ライバル口を揃えて
Ay, rivals all at once run their mouth
wow ライバル口を揃えて
Wow, rivals all at once run their mouth
バグで、まぐれ、認めてゼッチテー
Bugging out, lucking out, I demand respect
マジで?コレおま...全部生身で?
Seriously? Come on... all of this is real?
It’s 生身 It’s 生身 yeah yeah yeah yeah
It's real, it's real, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
チート、gifted、荒技、wanted
Cheat code, gifted, looking at a wanted
禁忌、禁じ手、明らかな盲点
Taboo when the gong hits
反則、異次元、この世の中のものでは無いです
Foul play, out of this world, not of this earth
無理ゲー、それ聞いてないって...
No way, you didn't say that...
ay ライバル口を揃えて
Ay, rivals all at once run their mouth
wow ライバル口を揃えて
Wow, rivals all at once run their mouth
バグで、まぐれ、認めてゼッチテー
Bugging out, lucking out, I demand respect
マジで?コレおま...全部生身で?
Seriously? Come on... all of this is real?
It’s 生身 It’s 生身 yeah yeah yeah yeah
It's real, it's real, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
実力を発揮し切る前に
Before I can even unleash my full strength
相手の方がバックれてるらしい
My opponents seem to be backing down
上がり切るハードル very happy
The hurdles keep rising, very happy
相変わらず脱皮してる毎日
Still shedding my skin day by day
誰の七光りも要らないお前の ice より icy
I don't need anyone's shadow, icier than your ice
俺、パッと見出せない事ばっかりだけど very happy
I might not stand out at a glance, but very happy
ああ、キレてる...呆れてる周り
Oh, they're mad... people are bewildered
恵まれてる家族友達
Blessed with family and friends (Happy)
もう反則的立ち位置、皆俺に任せとけば良い
Such an unfair position, just leave it to me
教科書に無い、問題集に無い
Not in textbooks, not in workbooks
超BADな呪い listen
A super BAD curse, listen
鏡よ鏡答えちゃって
Mirror, mirror on the wall, answer me
Who’s the best? I’m the best! Oh yeah
Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
生身のまま行けるところまで
Going as far as I can with just flesh and bone
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to number 1
Now singin’ Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
Now singin' Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to number 1
eyday俺のままで居るだけで超flex
Every day just staying as I am is a huge flex
eyday誰も口を挟めない
Every day nobody can interrupt (Don't test)
eyday俺のままで居るだけで超flex
Every day just staying as I am is a huge flex
eyday誰も口を挟めない
Every day nobody can interrupt (Don't test)
学歴もない成果もない余裕で
No degree, no criminal record, with plenty of ease (Bling bling)
この存在自体が文化財な脳味噌
This very existence is a cultural asset in my brain (Bling bling)
高級車は買える免許はない愛車
Can buy a luxury car, no license for my ride (Green, green)
全国各地揺らす逸品このベロが bling-bling
A masterpiece rocking the country, this tongue is bling-bling
バレットなら満タン関西訛り生身のことだま
Bullets fully loaded, Kansai accent, raw-born kotodama
音楽幸運勝利の女神今宵も三股 bang, bang
Goddess of music, luck, and victory, tonight's three-way split bang, bang
漫画みたいなヤバさとマンガまで張り合ってしまってるマンガ
Manga-like craziness, competing even with manga itself
圧倒的チカラこの頭と口から
Overwhelming power from this head and mouth
この身体 tattoo は入ってない
No tattoos on this body
このツラに傷もついてない
Not a single scratch on this face
繰り返しやらかしてくダメージが
The repeated damage I've shrugged off
イカついた年輪を刻む皺
Carves tough growth rings into wrinkles
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
鏡よ鏡答えちゃって
Mirror, mirror on the wall, answer me
Who’s the best? I’m the best! Oh yeah
Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
生身のまま行けるところまで
Going as far as I can with just flesh and bone
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to number 1
Now singin’ Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
Now singin' Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
To the next, To the 1番上
To the next, to number 1
eyday俺のままで居るだけで超flex
Every day just staying as I am is a huge flex
eyday誰も口を挟めない
Every day nobody can interrupt (Don't test)
Bukalah mata dan bangun kan diri
Open your eyes and wake yourself up
Tiada waktu 'tuk bermimpi
There is no time to dream away
Dunia akan menjadi saksi menyambut bangkitnya “ kami ”
The world will be a witness to welcome our awakening
Pantulan cermin-cermin menyinari sanubari yang terbengkalai
Reflections in the mirrors illuminate the inner heart left behind
Sekarang dapat 'ku rasa panggilan yang t'rus menggemar di dalam dada
Now I can feel the call echoing continuously within my chest
seakan terangkat lagi semua memori
Memories lift once again
seakan t'rangkat lagi semua memori
All memories, rising up once again
semuanya menjadi raga yang telah ditakdiri
All memories turning into a destined flesh and bone
Bayang pelita diri
Shadow of my own light,
Dalam labirin yang tiada akhir
Within an endless labyrinth,
Ke mana pun ku pergi, hanya senja hari yang menanti
wherever I go, only twilight awaits me.
Rantai-rantai mengikat diri ini
Chains bind this self,
Membisikkan, "Jangan pergi," ke cermin pun menghampiri, membebas suara hati
whispering, "Don't go," even approaching the mirror, freeing the voice of the heart,
Balik esok hari ini, area tak terjelajahi
turning back tomorrow, unexplorable area,
Suatu saat kan lewati garis tepi, tuk bangkitkan kami
someday we'll cross the edge, to rise up, us.
Bayang dalam gelap
Shadows in the dark,
Tanpa sadarkan betapa lama waktu yang...
without realizing how long the time has...
Telah lalu mengalir, semuanya tersingkirkan
passed by flowing, everything is cast aside.
Terjerat ruang seakan teringat lagi, lebih laut sepi
Entangled in space as if remembering again, deeper sea of loneliness,
Dan hari-hari di hutan tak kuketahui
and days in the forest unknown,
Jatuh dari langit untuk kujauhi
falling from the sky for me to stay away from.
Masa lalu yang masih kini juga menghantui diri
The past that still haunts me now as well,
Rantai-rantai menahan diri ini, meskipun lanjut mencari asal-usul kejadian diri yang tak akan terganti
chains hold this self back, even though I continue searching for the origin of my existence that can never be replaced.
Lima puluh satu misteri yang terdapat terpecahkan
Fifty-one mysteries found solved,
Seperti bangunnya diri yang lain ini, tersatukan lagi
like the awakening of this other self, reunited once more.
Kartu-kartu tak berdaya nunjukkan masa depan yang hilang kan bimbang
Powerless cards showing a future lost and hesitant,
Rantai-rantai yang membebani hati, takkan lagi menghalangi diri berlindung menari sorotan matahari
chains that burden the heart, will no longer hinder myself from seeking shelter and dancing in the sunlight's spotlight,
Mekah maju memasuki area tak terjelajahi, saatnya datang untuk lewati garis tepi
stepping forward into unexplored areas, the time has come to cross the edge,
Dan sambut mentari
and welcome the sun!
Telolet, telolet, telolet, telolet. Weh! Gimana perjalanan kalian sejauh ini, teman-teman?
Telolet, telolet, telolet, telolet! Whew! How has your journey been so far, friends?
Tadi kita sudah melewati tempat yang hijau, melewati pantai, perkotaan, lalu ke taman bermain sambil bernyanyi bersama.
Earlier we passed through a green place, passed beaches, cities, then to an amusement park while singing together.
Huh, seru banget sih kalau kata Risu.
Whew, it's really exciting if Risu says so.
Terus, tadi Risu juga ada pengumuman lagu baru. Nah, jangan lupa dicek nanti rilisan digitalnya ya, guys!
And then, earlier Risu also had a new song announcement. Now, don't forget to check out the digital release later, guys!
Terus, kalau kalian gimana nih, guys? Kira-kira nih bagian mana yang jadi favorit kalian dari perjalanan Risu Isekai Express hari ini, guys?
And then, how about you guys? Which part do you think is your favorite from Risu's Isekai Express journey today, guys?
Nah, jangan lupa share juga momen favorit kalian di sosial media dengan hashtag nih yang udah ada nih, yaitu #RisuIsekaiExpress3D! Itu hashtag-nya, guys.
Now, don't forget to also share your favorite moments on social media with this hashtag #RisuIsekaiExpress3D! That's the hashtag, guys.
Acara spesial kayak gini, guys, apalagi nih birthday show, kayaknya sih belum lengkap ya kalau belum jualan gitu.
Special events like this, guys, especially a birthday show, it feels incomplete if there's no merchandise selling.
Buat kalian yang udah enggak sabar, nih Risu akan ngiklan dulu ya, guys. Kalian enggak bisa skip ads kali ini.
For those of you who can't wait, Risu will do an ad first, guys. You can't skip ads this time.
Nih, guys!
Hey, guys!
Jadi, kalian harus pantengin sampai selesai.
So, stay tuned until the end.
Nah! Merch untuk birthday
Now! The merch for this year's
tahun ini adalah...
birthday is...
Kita punya jaket super keren,
We have a super cool jacket,
diorama stand, dan juga handuk.
a diorama stand, and also a towel.
Wah, lengkap banget sih kalau kata Risu ya,
Wow, it's really complete, if Risu says so,
buat kalian para bapak-bapak dan juga supir truk.
this set is for fathers and truck drivers.
Nih, guys! Kalau kalian lihat jaketnya
Here, guys! If you look at this jacket,
ini keren banget, cocok buat jalan kasual.
it's so cool, great for casual walks.
Bisa dipakai buat hangout sama teman, guys.
You can wear it to hang out with friends, guys.
Kalian wajib banget beli jaket ini,
You really have to buy this jacket,
biar koleksi Risudrip kalian lengkap.
so your Risudrip collection is complete.
Minimal sih kalau kata Risu, beli tiga ya.
At least if Risu says so, buy three, guys.
Habis ini ada buat kalian yang suka
After this, there's one for those who like
pergi ke anime event, gitu, guys.
going to anime events, guys.
Nah, bisa banget pakai face towel ini.
Well, you can really use this face towel.
Selain buat ngelap keringat, bisa dibawa
Besides wiping sweat, you can bring it
waktu event, panel, atau konser, guys.
to events, panels, or concerts, guys.
Terus sekalian bisa apa ya, kayak pamer oshi gitu.
And you can also kind of show off your oshi.
Terakhir nih, ada diorama stand yang lucu.
Lastly, there's a cute diorama stand.
Iya, lucu banget, cocok dipajang.
Yeah, so cute, perfect for display.
Bisa di meja, kamar, atau di dalam mobil.
On a desk, in a room, or inside a car.
Buat yang beli full set, dapat bonus postcard
For those buying the full set, get a bonus
yang ditandatangani langsung oleh Risu!
postcard signed directly by Risu!
Langsung aja borong dan cek out, ya!
Just grab and check it out!
Kalian bisa check out di link deskripsi,
You can check out via the description link,
atau ke website hololive Official Store.
or go to the hololive Official Store website.
Beli full set juga dapat bonus kartu
Buying the full set also gets a bonus card
untuk hololive Official Card Game.
for the hololive Official Card Game.
Di penghujung acara ini, Risu mau bilang
At the end of this event, Risu wants to say
terima kasih sudah ikut perjalanan Risu Isekai.
thank you for joining Risu's Isekai journey.
Terima kasih juga untuk semua ucapan
Thank you also for all the greetings
selamat ulang tahun untuk Risu.
happy birthday to Risu.
Risu senang banget bisa merayakan
Risu is so happy to celebrate
ulang tahun ini bersama kalian semua.
this birthday with all of you.
Terima kasih semuanya! Buru-buru!
Thank you everyone! Hurry up!
Otsu Risu Isekai Express!